The blue triangle right here represents the milk category.
Now milk is essential for growth of teeth and bones.
The recommended allowance for children ages four to five is two to three cups.
Now, once over two, children can safely switch from vitamin D whole milk to things like reduced fat or even skim milk.
As long as they're healthy and staying in good physically active conditions.
Now, many parents are giving their kids soda, and tea, and fruit juices, and forgetting how important milk is.
Good habits must start young, and they also start with you.
If kids see you drinking milk, they're going to drink milk, and they're going to put down the soda.
Now, one cup of milk is obviously one cup of milk, or a cup of yogurt counts also.
If you're looking at things like processed cheese, one slice is enough for one cup.
Things like American, and mozzarella, things like that.
Or a half an ounce of hard cheese, things like cheddar, swiss, mozzarella, things that come in like the little logs of cheese.
And that's what we have on milk.